Guide to the United Student Christian Council Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- World Student Christian Federation, Series VII
  - WSCF Commissions
    - Ecumenical and University Commission
      - University Commission, Correspondence, circular letters, memos, notes, and reports, 1947 (Box 104, Folder 1227)
      - University Commission, Planning for joint seminar on the Church-Related College sponsored by World Council of Christian Education and WSCF, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 1228)
    - Political Commission
      - Circular letters Sharing Information, 1947-1950 (Box 104, Folder 1229)
      - Circular letters Sharing Information, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1230)
      - Correspondence, Jones, Penry, Maury, Philippe, Thomas, M.M., and Wen-Han, Kiang, 1946-1949 (Box 104, Folder 1231)
      - Correspondence, Maury, Philippe, 1947-1948 (Box 104, Folder 1232)
      - Correspondence, Student Christian groups in the U.S.A., 1948 (Box 104, Folder 1233)
      - Memos, General Assembly of the United Nations, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 1234)
      - Political Consultation, Bievres, France, meeting agenda, notes, and reports, August 17-22, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 1235)
      - Reports re. Political Commission, 1947-1948 (Box 105, Folder 1236)
      - Research materials including pamphlets British Citizens in World Affairs, Christian Obedience in Post-War Britain, and Toward Mutual Understanding: The Story of UNESCO, 1947-1948 (Box 105, Folder 1237)
  - Publications and Printed Material
    - Circular letters re. world student relief, 1946 (Box 105, Folder 1238)
    - Circular letters to general secretaries, 1946-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1239)
    - Constitution of Worlds Student Christian Federation, n.d. (Box 105, Folder 1240)
    - Consultative meeting, Poughkeepsie, NY, February 1942 (Box 105, Folder 1241)
    - Directories, 1947, 1950, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 1242)
    - Memos re. Inter-Varsity Fellowship of Evangelical Fellowship Unions, World Christian Youth Commission, WSCF finances, etc., 1946-1953 (Box 105, Folder 1243)
    - Memos re. International seminar on Christian faith and political questions in Burma, 1955 (Box 105, Folder 1244)
    - Memos re. Life and Mission of the Church emphasis, 1957 (Box 106, Folder 1245)
    - Minutes, Executive committee, 1946-1950 (Box 106, Folder 1246)
    - Minutes, Executive committee, 1951-1953 (Box 106, Folder 1247)
    - Minutes, European council, 1947, 1950 (Box 106, Folder 1248)
    - News Releases, circa 1946-1947 (Box 106, Folder 1249)
    - Pamphlets including The Asian Leaders' Conference: an Interpretation by M.M. Thomas, A Living Record: a Bird's Eye View of the Bible and Hints for Study, Times of Testing: Impressions of the Life of the World's Student Christian Federation in the War Years, A Visit to the Far East: a Travel Diary by Helen Morton, 1944-1957 (Box 106, Folder 1250)
    - Pamphlets re. Life and Mission of the Church emphasis, 1957-1960 (Box 106, Folder 1251)
    - Reports, 3 year report of WSCF: Out of Weakness Made Strong: a Report on the Life of the National Student Christian Movements related to the World's Student Christian Federation during the years 1938 to 1946 includes provisional edition and The Federation Turns the Corner a Survey from August 1944 to July 1946 (Box 106, Folder 1252)
    - Reports, 3 year report of the WSCF: Unto a Lively Hope: a Report on the Life of the World's Student Christian Federation and Related National Student Christian Movements During the Years 1946 to 1949 and Witnessing to Jesus Christ the Reconciler: a Report on the Life of the WSCF and Related National S.C.M.s during the Years 1953-1956, 1949, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 1253)
    - Reports, re. Asian student Christian movement, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 1254)
    - Reports, re. Commissions, 1956 (Box 107, Folder 1255)
    - Reports, re. Conferences, 1947-1954 (Box 107, Folder 1256)
    - Reports, miscellaneous, 1952-1955 (Box 107, Folder 1257)
    - Reports, miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 107, Folder 1258)
    - Reports, re. Missions, 1949 (Box 107, Folder 1259)
    - Reports, Report on Schools Work within the World's Student Christian Federation compiled by Bengt Hoffman, July 1947 (Box 107, Folder 1260)
    - Reports, re. student Christian movements, 1946-1947 (Box 107, Folder 1261)
    - Reports, re. student Christian movements, 1947-1948 (Box 107, Folder 1262)
    - Reports, re. student Christian movements, 1948-1953 (Box 108, Folder 1263)
    - Reports, "Report of a Working Party on the Racial Problem in South Africa", 1956 (Box 108, Folder 1264)
  - Student Christian Movement in Other Countries
    - Australia, Correspondence and The Australian Intercollegian: the Journal of the Australian Student Christian Movement vol. LV, No. 3, 1951-1952 (Box 148, Folder 1693)
    - Austria, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 1694)
    - Baltic region, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 1695)
    - Belgium sCm, Circular letters and newsletter A.B.A.: Bulletin de L'Association Belgo-Americaine (all materials in French), l947 (Box 148, Folder 1696)
    - Brazil, Circular letter and periodical Excelsior: Órgão Oficial da União Crista de Estudantes do Brasil, 1950-1952 (Box 148, Folder 1697)
    - Burma, Annual reports, correspondence, and directory, 1948-1952 (Box 148, Folder 1698)
    - Canada, Correspondence, 1946-1948 (Box 148, Folder 1699)
    - Canada, Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 148, Folder 1700)
    - Canada, Minutes and Reports from the National Council of the Student Christian Movement of Canada, 1947, 1949, 1952 (Box 148, Folder 1701)
    - Canada, Newsletters, papers, and reports including Bias and Imprint: Magazine of the Student Christian Movement of Canada, 1950-1956 (Box 148, Folder 1702)
    - Chile, Letter to Raymond Valenznela from John Deschner, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 1703)
    - Ceylon (now Sri Lanka), Correspondence, 1948-1957 (Box 149, Folder 1704)
    - Ceylon (now Sri Lanka), Pamphlets, periodical, and report including The Pilgrim: a Bi-Annual Publication of the Student Christian Movement of Ceylon, 1957-1960 (Box 149, Folder 1705)
    - China, Correspondence and letters includes reports by Kiang Wen-Han and newspaper clippings re. murder of Yu Tse-sen by the Hangchow Peace Preservation Police, 1945-1951 (Box 149, Folder 1706)
    - China, Newsletters and periodicals including NSRC Newsletter and Today's China, 1947-1949 (Box 149, Folder 1707)
    - Cuba, Newsletter, Nike vol. 1 no. 1, April 1960 (Box 149, Folder 1708)
    - Czechoslovakia, Correspondence, 1948-1952 (Box 149, Folder 1709)
    - Czechoslovakia, Newsletters, pamphlets including Bulletin of the Evangelical Church of Czech Brethren (Presbyterian Church in Bohemia and Moravia) and Krestanska Revue, 1946-1950 (Box 149, Folder 1710)
    - Denmark, Brochures and newsletter, 1959, n.d. (Box 149, Folder 1711)
    - Estonia, Circular letter and Newsletter from Behind the Iron Curtain: Reports on communist Activities in Eastern Europe, 1948 (Box 149, Folder 1712)
    - Finland, Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 149, Folder 1713)
    - France, Correspondence some re. French asking how the Americans view German rearmament, 1946-1952 (Box 149, Folder 1714)
    - France, Brochures, journal Le Semeur, and report on construction of a Protestant student center, 1956, 1962 (Box 150, Folder 1715)
    - Germany, Correspondence includes report from a traveling secretary of the Evangelische Studentengemeinde, 1945, 1947-1953 (Box 150, Folder 1716)
    - Germany, Miscellaneous publications including journals Mitteilungen der Evangelischen Studentengemeinde in Deutschland, Der Christliche Student, and Ansätze, 1947-1949, 1956 (Box 150, Folder 1717)
    - Greece, Correspondence, miscellaneous publications including Greek Orthodox News Sheet: Issued by the Student Christian Association of Greece, 1948-1952 (Box 150, Folder 1718)
    - Guatemala, Correspondence, 1949 (Box 150, Folder 1719)
    - Haiti, Correspondence, 1950 (Box 150, Folder 1720)
    - Holland, Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 150, Folder 1721)
    - Hong Kong, Annual report and pamphlet Why a Student Christian Center, 1957, 1958 (Box 150, Folder 1722)
    - Hungary, Letter, 1947 (Box 150, Folder 1723)
    - India, Correspondence, 1945-1952 (Box 150, Folder 1724)
    - India, Correspondence, Daniel, Harry, 1953-1955 (Box 150, Folder 1725)
    - India, Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 150, Folder 1726)
    - India, Aikya: a National Student Paper, 1955-1959, 1962 (Box 151, Folder 1727)
    - India, Journal, Darshan, 1955-1956 (Box 151, Folder 1728)
    - India, miscellaneous publications including annual reports of the sCm of India, India's Quest for Democracy edited by P.D. Devanandan and M.M. Thomas, Minutes of the Meeting of the General Committee of the Student Christian Movement of India, and Youth News: a Bulletin Issued periodically by the Central Youth Committee of the National Christian Council of India, 1954-1957 (Box 151, Folder 1729)
    - India, Student Outlook: the Official Organ of the student Christian Movement of India, Pakistan and Ceylon, 1947, 1948, 1951, 1954 (Box 151, Folder 1730)
    - Indonesian group in the Netherlands, Correspondence and periodical Kesaksian, 1950-1952 (Box 151, Folder 1731)
    - Italy, Newsletter News from Agape, 1959, 1960 (Box 151, Folder 1732)
    - Jamaica, Letter and periodical Victory, 1951, 1962 (Box 151, Folder 1733)
    - Japan, Correspondence includes letters from Ruth Seabury, 1945, 1947-1951 (Box 151, Folder 1734)
    - Japan, Correspondence re. hydrogen bomb testing at Bikini atoll, 1954 (Box 151, Folder 1735)
    - Japan, Miscellaneous publications including an issue of Kaitakusha (The Pioneer), 1949, 1956 (Box 151, Folder 1736)
    - Korea, Correspondence and reports, 1948-1951 (Box 151, Folder 1737)
    - Latin America, Correspondence and reports, 1950-1955 (Box 151, Folder 1738)
    - Malaysia, Report, 1954 (Box 151, Folder 1739)
    - Mexico, Correspondence re. Betty Johns traveling to Mexico on behalf of WSCF and miscellaneous publications including Ariel: Boletin de la Associacion Cristiana de Estudiant es de Mexico and Seminario: Foro del Pensamiento y Espirtu Estudiantil, 1947-1952 (Box 151, Folder 1740)
    - New Zealand, Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 151, Folder 1741)
    - New Zealand, Student: Journal of the New Zealand Christian Movement, 1950, 1953-1957, 1959 (Box 152, Folder 1742)
    - Nigeria, Reports including "Report of a Consultation on Student Christian Work in West Africa", 1956 (Box 152, Folder 1743)
    - Norway, Correspondence includes bible study and pamphlet Hva er Mennesket? [What is Man?], 1949-1952 (Box 152, Folder 1744)
    - Pakistan, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 1745)
    - Philippine Islands, Brochures, correspondence, newsletters, and reports including For the Philippines SCM: a Student Christian Movement Handbook, 1945, 1949-1955 (Box 152, Folder 1746)
    - Poland, Letters, 1948-1949 (Box 152, Folder 1747)
    - Puerto Rico, Correspondence, newsletters, Guacio Newsletter and Colegiales Xnos: Boletín de la Federacion de Colgiales Cristianos, 1948, 1950-1951, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 1748)
    - Russian sCm in France, Correspondence, journal The Messenger, and reports, 1949, 1951, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 1749)
    - Sierra Leone, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 152, Folder 1750)
    - Singapore, Letters, 1950 (Box 152, Folder 1751)
    - Southern Rhodesia, Brochures for a camp in Southern Rhodesia, n.d. (Box 152, Folder 1752)
    - South Africa, Correspondence, miscellaneous publications including annual reports and newsletters, Africa Today: Bulletin of the American Committee on Africa, The SCA Newsletter, and Sigma: Official organ of the English Medium Work of the Student Christian Association of South Africa, 1946-1958 (Box 152, Folder 1753)
    - Student Christian Movement of Great Britain and Ireland, Correspondence, 1946-1952 (Box 152, Folder 1754)
    - Student Christian Movement of Great Britain and Ireland, Annual reports, booklets Christian Obedience in the University and Study Groups and their Leadership, and a study outline for medical students, 1946-1959 (Box 153, Folder 1755)
    - Student Christian Movement of Great Britain and Ireland, Journals, Encounter: a Bulletin of International Student Interests and The Student Movement, 1950-1959 (Box 153, Folder 1756)
    - Sweden, Correspondence and report, 1946-1950, 1952 (Box 153, Folder 1757)
    - Thailand, Letter, 1950 (Box 153, Folder 1758)
    - Tunisia, pamphlet on reconstruction, 1946 (Box 153, Folder 1759)
- Denominational and YMCA Correspondence and Publications, Series VIII
  - Correspondence
    - Congregational Christian Church: Division of Christian Education, 1945-1952 (Box 129, Folder 1512)
    - Disciples of Christ:: Board of Mission and Education, 1946-1952 (Box 129, Folder 1513)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church: Board of Christian Education and Publication, 1946-1952 (Box 129, Folder 1514)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church: Board of Christian Education and Publication, 1955-1956 (Box 130, Folder 1515)
    - Evangelical United Brethren: Board of Christian Education, 1948-1952 (Box 130, Folder 1516)
    - Lutheran Student Association of America, 1946-1950 (Box 130, Folder 1517)
    - Lutheran Student Association of America, 1950-1952 (Box 130, Folder 1518)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Education, 1945-1947 (Box 130, Folder 1519)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Education, 1948-1949 (Box 130, Folder 1520)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Education, 1950 (Box 130, Folder 1521)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Education, 1951 (Box 130, Folder 1522)
    - Methodist Church: Board of Education, 1951-1952 (Box 130, Folder 1523)
    - National Intercollegiate Christian Council (memos), 1945-1946 (Box 131, Folder 1524)
    - NICC, 1946-1947 (Box 131, Folder 1525)
    - NICC, 1947-1948 (Box 131, Folder 1526)
    - NICC, 1949-1952 (Box 131, Folder 1527)
    - NICC, assembly, 1950-1951 (Box 131, Folder 1528)
    - Northern Baptist Convention: Board of Education and Publication, 1946-1949 (Box 131, Folder 1529)
    - Northern Baptist Convention: Board of Education and Publication, 1949-1952 (Box 131, Folder 1530)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Joint Committee on Student Work, 1945-1948 (Box 131, Folder 1531)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Joint Committee on Student Work and Department of Student Work, 1949-1950 (Box 131, Folder 1532)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Department of Student Work, 1951 (Box 131, Folder 1533)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Board of Education, 1951-1952 (Box 132, Folder 1534)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Board of Education, 1953-1959 (Box 132, Folder 1535)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.: Board of Education re. conferences, 1954-1957 (Box 132, Folder 1536)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1945-1948 (Box 132, Folder 1537)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1948-1949 (Box 132, Folder 1538)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1949-1950 (Box 132, Folder 1539)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1950-1951 (Box 132, Folder 1540)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1951-1952 (Box 132, Folder 1541)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Board of Christian Education, 1953-1959 (Box 132, Folder 1542)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Student Work Survey Committee, 1951 (Box 132, Folder 1543)
    - Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A.: Student Work Survey Committee, 1952 (Box 133, Folder 1544)
    - Protestant Episcopal: Division of College Work, 1945-1952 (Box 133, Folder 1545)
    - Protestant Episcopal: Division of College Work, 1953-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1546)
    - United Campus Christian Fellowship merger includes reports, 1955-1956 (Box 133, Folder 1547)
    - United Student Fellowship of the United Church of Christ, 1948-1952 (Box 133, Folder 1548)
    - United Student Fellowship of the United Church of Christ, 1954-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1549)
    - YMCA, 1946-1946 (Box 133, Folder 1550)
    - YMCA, 1947-1952 (Box 133, Folder 1551)
    - YMCA: Preparatory School Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 133, Folder 1552)
    - YMCA, 1953-1959 (Box 133, Folder 1553)
    - YMCA and YWCA regional groups, 1952-1955, 1958 (Box 134, Folder 1554)
    - YWCA, 1945-1948 (Box 134, Folder 1555)
    - YWCA, 1948-1952 (Box 134, Folder 1556)
    - YWCA, 1953-1959 (Box 134, Folder 1557)
  - Publications and Printed Materials
    - Congregational Christian, Brochures and pamphlets including Historical Sketches of the Congregational Christian Churches and the Evangelical and Reformed Church and The Department of Religion in a College or University by Bryant Drake, 1947-1958 (Box 134, Folder 1558)
    - Congregational Christian, Newsletter Student Life Notes and Department of Higher Education Congregational Christian Churches Newsletter, 1946-1948 (Box 134, Folder 1559)
    - Congregational Christian, Department of Higher Education Congregational Christian Churches Newsletter, 1949-1952 (Box 134, Folder 1560)
    - Congregational Christian, Department of Higher Education Congregational Christian Churches Newsletter, 1952-1959 (Box 134, Folder 1561)
    - Congregational Christian, Program Manual for Workers with Students, n.d. (Box 134, Folder 1562)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Brochures, 1948, 1950, n.d. (Box 134, Folder 1563)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Conference materials for 1949 Quadrennial Conference includes book Whence and Whither the Disciples of Christ by Wilfred Ernest Garrison (Box 134, Folder 1564)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Mailing list, 1947-1948, 1950 (Box 134, Folder 1565)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter DSF Journal, 1950-1951 (Box 135, Folder 1566)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter DSF Journal, 1951-1952 (Box 135, Folder 1567)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter DSF Journal, 1952-1953 (Box 135, Folder 1568)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter DSF Journal, 1954-1956 (Box 135, Folder 1569)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter The Student Work Bulletin, 1947-1949 (Box 135, Folder 1570)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter The Student Work Bulletin, 1950 (Box 135, Folder 1571)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter The Student Work Bulletin, 1951-1952 (Box 135, Folder 1572)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter The Student Work Bulletin, 1954-1955 (Box 136, Folder 1573)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Newsletter The Student Work Bulletin, 1955-1956 (Box 136, Folder 1574)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Social Action Idea Book: for Christian Church Student Groups, Disciples of Christ Student Fellowships, Bethany Fellowships, and Other College Age Groups (Box 136, Folder 1575)
    - Disciples of Christ Student Fellowship, Student Workers Association Conference Report, 1949-1950, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 1576)
    - Evangelical and Reformed Church, Brochures, Evangelical and Reformed Student News-Letter, periodical The Messenger, and Report on History and Essential Beliefs of the Evangelical and Reformed Church by Eva Mosher, 1947-1948, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 1577)
    - Lutheran Student Association of America, Advent and Lent meditations (Box 136, Folder 1578)
    - LSAA, Brochures, 1946-1950 (Box 136, Folder 1579)
    - LSAA, Council Minutes of the Lutheran Student Association of America and materials for Consultation on International Exchange, 1948, 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 136, Folder 1580)
    - LSAA, Newsletters Lutheran Faculty and LSAA Monthly Bulletin, 1948-1949, 1954, 1955 (Box 136, Folder 1581)
    - LSAA, Newsletters miscellaneous college campuses, 1948-1952 (Box 136, Folder 1582)
    - LSAA, Scoop Newsletter, 1954-1956 (Box 137, Folder 1583)
    - LSAA, Newsletter Staff Letters: Division of Student Service National Lutheran Council, 1950-1951 (Box 137, Folder 1584)
    - LSAA, Newsletter Staff Letters: Division of Student Service National Lutheran Council, 1951-1952 (Box 137, Folder 1585)
    - LSAA, Newsletter Student Service Bulletin, 1947-1949 (Box 137, Folder 1586)
    - LSAA, Periodical American Lutheran Student, 1946-1949 (Box 137, Folder 1587)
    - LSAA, Pamphlets including Go Into All the World: an Introduction to Lutheran Missions by Fredrik A. Schiotz, Basic Questions for the Christian Scholar by Jerald C. Brauer, and Fishers of Men by Walter Schmidt, 1947-1952 (Box 137, Folder 1588)
    - LSAA, Pamphlets, Preparation for What? by Paul W. Dieckman and hymn booklets (Box 137, Folder 1589)
    - LSAA, Paper, "Basic Questions for the Christian Scholar: a Preface to Study and Discussion" prepared by Jerald C. Brauer, Ph.D., 1954 (Box 137, Folder 1590)
    - LSAA, Script for filmstrip Lutheran Student Action (filmstrip not included), 1949 (Box 137, Folder 1591)
    - LSAA, Student information packet includes various brochures, pamphlets, etc, 1949-1950 (Box 138, Folder 1592)
    - LSAA, Study booklets including The Glory of Common Tasks by Karl E. Mattson, The Bible: a Preface to Study by Richard R. Sayre, and We Believe: a Discussion Booklet for Lutheran Students of America by William Larsen, 1947-1952 (Box 138, Folder 1593)
    - LSAA, Study booklets Basic Christian Ethics: a Syllabus for Group Study prepared by George W. Forell, Introduction to the New Testament: a Syllabus for Group Study prepared by Warren A. Quanbeck, and The Lutheran Reformation: a Syllabus for Group Study by Jerald C. Brauer, 1952, 1955 (Box 138, Folder 1594)
    - LSAA, Workbook for Lutheran Student Groups, n.d. (Box 138, Folder 1595)
    - Methodist, Brochures, 1948-1957 (Box 138, Folder 1596)
    - Methodist, Directory of the Methodist Student Movement, 1948-1952 (Box 138, Folder 1597)
    - Methodist, Lecture, "Morals, Religion, and Higher Education" by Robert M. Hutchins and Minutes of the National Methodist Student Commission (Student Section of the National Conference of Methodist Youth), 1949, August 17-24, 1956 (Box 138, Folder 1598)
    - Methodist, Newsletter The Methodist Student Bulletin, 1947-1949 (Box 139, Folder 1599)
    - Methodist, Newsletter The Methodist Student Bulletin, 1949-1950 (Box 139, Folder 1600)
    - Methodist, Newsletter The Methodist Student Bulletin, 1950-1951 (Box 139, Folder 1601)
    - Methodist, Newsletter The Methodist Student Bulletin, 1952-1955 (Box 139, Folder 1602)
    - Methodist, Newsletters miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 139, Folder 1603)
    - Methodist, Reports on the Methodist Student Movement and a Survey of the Religious Program of some Mid-Western Universities, 1945, 1948, 1954 (Box 139, Folder 1604)
    - Methodist, Standards for Methodist Student Work (Box 139, Folder 1605)
    - Methodist, Travel diaries of H.D. Bollinger, 1948, 1953 (Box 139, Folder 1606)
    - National Intercollegiate Christian Council, booklets including Synopsis and Study Outline for the book the Crisis in the University by Sir Walter Moberly and Freedom and Order: National Intercollegiate Christian Council Staff Study Guide, 1945-1948, 1957 (Box 140, Folder 1607)
    - NICC, Conference materials, 1946-1947 (Box 140, Folder 1608)
    - NICC, Conference materials, 1949-1950 (Box 140, Folder 1609)
    - NICC, Conference materials, 1951 (Box 140, Folder 1610)
    - NICC, Minutes of the Administrative Committee, 1946-1950 (Box 140, Folder 1611)
    - NICC, Minutes of the Administrative Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 140, Folder 1612)
    - NICC, Minutes of the Effective Citizenship Committee, 1949 (Box 140, Folder 1613)
    - NICC, Minutes of miscellaneous committees, 1945-1946 (Box 140, Folder 1614)
    - NICC, Minutes of the Program Committee, 1946-1950 (Box 140, Folder 1615)